http://www.dynamicsignal.com/privacy/

Request a DemoPlatformFeaturesServicesSecurityDemo CenterSolutionsCommunicationHuman ResourcesMarketingHealthcareManufacturingRetailTechnologyInsuranceFinancial ServicesTransportationAgencyCustomersCase StudiesTestimonialsCompanyTeamCareersJob ListingsEventsPartnersResourcesBlogNews & PressEvents & WebinarsContactSupportSearch PrivacyLegal OverviewPrivacyOverviewWebsite / Marketing Privacy PolicyPlatform Privacy PolicyDySi Open Privacy PolicyGDPR ReadinessTermsOverviewPlatform Terms of UseDySi Open Terms of UseSaaS AgreementService Level Agreement (SLA)Third Party SubprocessorsThird Party API Terms Of ServiceData Protection AgreementADAADA Compliance StatementDMCAReporting Intellectual Property ViolationsDynamic Signal, Inc. (“DySi”, “us”, “our”, or “we”) is a technology company and provides cloud-based services (which include websites, mobile apps, and other technology and services) dedicated to employee communications and engagement.
Our Privacy Policies are tailored for the different ways personal information is collected from individuals who visit our web and mobile sites or apps and/or who use any of our services or otherwise interact with us.
The Website and Marketing Privacy Policy addresses information we collect at our web sites and in general sales and marketing activities, as a controller.
The Platform Privacy Policy addresses customer data to which we may be provided access through provision of our SaaS Platform service on behalf of a customer, as a sub-processor.
The DySi Open Privacy Policy addresses information we collect through our DySi Open app and website, as a controller.
If your use of any of our services requires DySi to process personal data falling within the scope of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), DySi’s Data Processing Addendum is available for review here.
Additionally, more information about our efforts to prepare for the GDPR, please visit our GDPR page.
If you have any concerns or questions about how your personal data is used, please contact us at privacy@dynamicsignal.com. We will promptly respond to address your concern.
